<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef Abstract="true" Name="WBR_UpdateFeatureBase">
		<modNameReadable>Way Better Romance</modNameReadable>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="WBR_UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>WBR_OrderedHookups</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.1.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>&lt;b&gt;Ordered hookups are here!&lt;/b&gt;\n\nExtremely similar to the forced romance attempts added with Biotech, you can now order your colonists to attempt a hookup. (Biotech is not required for this feature.) There is a 20% increase to acceptance of an ordered hookup. This is multiplicative, so a success chance of 0% won't be affected.\n\nSettings can be added by race modders to limit how their race uses this system. This includes a minimum opinion requirement, breeding only, trait requirements, or disabling it altogether.\n\nAlong with this update there are some new user settings.\n\nFertility Mod: If you have a mod that adds pregnancy (including Biotech) please set it here. Some of these mods can be used together, and I need to know which one is actually handling fertility. If your mod is not on the list, please let me know what mod you're using on steam or github.\n\nAdd joy need to slaves and/or prisoners. Having a joy need is a requirement for regular hookups. So if you want your slaves or prisoners to hook up with each other, use these settings to give them a joy need. If you change the setting while playing, you'll need to reload the save for it to take effect.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="WBR_UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>WBR_LoverPrecepts</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.2.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>&lt;b&gt;New precepts added!&lt;/b&gt;|One addition to the spouse count precepts, no spouses, so that no one will ever get married. And then a new issue, lover count, to supplement spouses.|Previously, all love relationships (spouse, fiance, lover, and any custom relations) were limited by the spouse count precept.|Now, only spouse and fiance are limited by the spouse count precept, and then the lover count precept is added to that. So an individual whose ideoligion allows two spouses and three lovers can have five love relations total, but can only marry two of them. This enables an additional way to make people not care about cheating without having to use Lovin' - free and approved. Just allow unlimited lovers!|To keep the previous behavior, just set the lover count to zero, which is the default.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="WBR_UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>WBR_EditSexRepulsion</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.2.1</assemblyVersion>
		<content>&lt;b&gt;New orientation info pane, plus changing sex repulsion in dev mode!&lt;/b&gt;|First off, there's now a place in game to get detailed information about a pawn's orientation. Access it by simply clicking on the trait in the Bio tab.|img:Images/OrientationPane1|Here you'll see an explanation of the exact effect of the pawn's sex repulsion. Right now this is only available for asexual orientations, but some day it may be added to the others.|img:Images/OrientationPane2|If you have dev mode enabled, you'll see a very special option at the top of this pane.|img:Images/OrientationPane3|Using the slider you can change the pawn's sex repulsion. Enjoy!</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
</Defs>